(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-10T23:37:03.566548",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hi, I'm Gigi Murin! I used to be 14 years old in 8th grade, but now I'm not!
I'm a bit clumsy, crazy, and silly,
and I may not look it, but actually, I'm a member of Hololive English -Justice-!
That's true.
I call myself the fister, because of my big, big power lift...
I don't really like that I call myself the fister, and I don't really know why...
...literally called the fister, because I fist people, you know? You know what I mean?
Today is the day of a very important Justice meeting,
but I accidentally overslept!
So I have to hurry up and...
...make sure to look both ways before crossing the road, and...
...go— Aaaah!
Gigi goes flying!
Ouch!
Who was that? That was so weird.
Wow.
Where am I?
A beautiful 2D fantasy world?
That was so efficient. She got hit by a car.
Let me tell you, that was awesome...
...hit them with a car, and it would be really cool... Wait, what the—
A horse? That's not a truck!
That's dangerous! I could have died!
But phew! That grem sure knows how to drive.
Grem enja— Aaaah!
Ah... ah...
Ouch, my body hurts.
I feel like I got run over by something, but I don't know what.
Oh.
Is that a statue of a Grem? Looks cool.
Wait a second...
I know this!
I've been isekai'd!
What the freak? Gigi, you're here too?
Is this Justice cardboard?
Gigi, what's going on?
Where are we?
Ouch... What are you guys doing? Why are you cardboard?
Why does CC look so sad?
You f***ing b***h! How dare you do this to me, you b***h!
This is your fault somehow! I don't know how you did this, you absolute little dumb f***! Oh, you look terrible.
Rude!
Well, let's go investigate around here.
Let's go.
Okay.
I'm on my way! Wait guys! Wait for me!
We can have an adventure together!
It'll be so fun, and, and, and...
Wait, wait, wait... What's going on?
Aaaah!
Horses...
Two of them...
Aaaah!
Goodbye...
Leaving heartbreak of the past behind.
Turning back, it's time.
Moving down our own paths,
ever voyaging forward to make this journey last.
Never spoken about in the light,
like a promise found riding the wind.
Where a myth begins spiraling outward and up,
an inspiring tale begins.
Who would dare defy changing of times,
as we follow unreachable dreams?
No, it's here and right now that we're drawn to somehow,
deep inside, a will to live that won't leave.
Let our fates awaken...
Wandering near and far,
touching lives just like ours.
Guiding fire till life's wasted away.
One day,
I'll recall these nights,
our relentless honesty.
Pressing onward,
we never surrender.
Toward the skies,
we can rise again.
Again...
I was hit by a truck and reincarnated as the protagonist in a fantasy world but then a horse ran me over and now all my friends are cardboard?
[Title: I was hit by a truck and reincarnated as the protagonist in a fantasy world but then a horse ran me over and now all my friends are cardboard?]
Uuugh...
If anything else hits me, I don't think I'll survive much longer.
I really need to be more careful.
Thank goodness I'm still alive.
The winds whispered of your coming...
And now, here you are.
Who are you?!
I am the greatest wizard in all of Grem Kingdom!
Wizard Oji-chan.
Wizard Oji-chan? Are you a wizard or Oji-chan? Do you have a name? What should I call you?
So many of Grem's warriors have fallen, one by one, while we waited for your arrival...
The wait was worth it!
You are far more powerful than I ever imagined a hero could be!
He's not responding to me. He's probably an NPC. Is this like a game? Am I in a game?
NPC?!
NPC? Show some respect! I'm a noble wizard! Oji-chan!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, I didn't know you could talk!
You're the key.
Without you, your friend and this world are lost...
What? Lost? What are you talking about?
Gigi, the world is waiting...
He knows my name! That's me. I'm the hero. I'm gonna save the world from being cardboard.
Hazaah!
What did you do to me?! It hurts! It hurts!
あれ？おかしい。何言ってんだ。これ。おかしい。
Wait... strange. What are you saying? Why...
Hazaah!
Wow, I feel so cute and soft and fluffy now! Friends with you? Purchase next time they're in stock.
あ、気持ち悪い？ごめん。もう一回やらせて。ちゃんと、今度、今度ちゃんとやるから。
Ah, do you feel sick? Sorry. Let me try once more. I'll do it properly this time!
I don't understand...
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
Haaaaazaah!
Hazaah!
Squeak! Squeak squeak! Squeak!
一回、一回！オッケー、オッケー、アイムレディー！
Once more, once more! Okay, okay, I'm ready!
ジシ！ジシ？レディー！バー！
Jishi! Jishi? Ready! Baaa!
Hazaah!
Ah... ah... ah...
Oh wait, I think I can move now! What is...
What is this?
Hands?!
You did it! You've done it!
Oh my god!
Look how... how cute I am!
Aw, I've always been cute. But now, now it's even- now everyone can see how cute I-
Look at that fat tail! Look at that fat ta-
I can do everything!
I can't do that.
Watch this, guys. Have you ever seen this before?
Okay, okay.
Whee! Whee! I can do everything.
Two in a row? Just kidding.
I have a world to save.
Look at that, everyone loves me!
Gigi Murin!
おっ、疲れた。よいしょ。
Oh, I'm tired. There we go.
Oh, I'm so dizzy.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What... what should I do to save everyone?
Oh, the world is spinning. Owy.
Before saving everyone...
...let's see if you can survive basic chores.
Basic... I can do basic chores.
Let's start with...
Huh?
Start with what? Start with what?
What?
What are we starting with?
Wing?
Birds! Birds! What?
Wait, what?
Old geezer! What are you doing with the birds? Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Old geezer, don't! Don't!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait!
No!
Aaaaah!
The birds took him! I knew I could never trust a bird!
Hey you, Come here! Follow me!
Um...
I have to help my... my friend.
You're scared and lost... Not knowing what to do, right?
I'll show you how to save your friends. Follow me!
Oh, okay.
You're so small.
This is weird.
This place is dark and it smells bad.
Hey it smells good!!!! Do exactly as I say if you want to save your friends!
Go to the Grem Kingdom and return with the One Ping, a Honkshoe, and a Straw Hat.
Why do you need them?
YOU DON'T GET TO ASK ME ANY QUESTIONS!!! NOW GO GIGI, GOOOOOO!!
Okay.
Wow!
So this is the Grem Kingdom?
It's so cool! There's so many Grems!
Does this mean this entire kingdom is mine if I save it?
Wow, so many of you.
Oh, not all at once! No, no, no, no.
What?
Oh, I can't hear you.
Let's... let's try this Grem. Lucky little Grem, what's on your mind?
Things aren't going well with my partner... I need your help to fix our relationship.
Aw... That is not my problem.
Ah, okay. How about this Grem? Do you have anything interesting to say to me?
My tummy is getting very large and I don't know why. Please come with me to the doctor.
Okay, a little... little secret. Pregnant.
Okay, how about this one?
Make a contract with me, and become a magical girl!
Oh, that is not my problem either. Oh, no, no, no, no.
I will not be doing that. I know what happens when you sign a contract!
You should never put your name down on things.
Well, these Grems were useless.
I think if I use my RPG knowledge...
...you're supposed to get information from NPCs...
...at a store! And there are so many stalls near me.
Ah! Let's go to this one.
[Gasp] So cute! Aw...
Are you a little worker Grem? Are you?
How much do you make an hour?
Do you make enough to survive? Aw...
Oh, what is this?
For me?
Uh, that's decorative hay, not edible...
Can I ask you something?
Oh, what is this? Dialogue.
Box?
Um...
Where can I get The One Ping?
Oh, you are looking for the One Ping?
Then, here is the Quest for you! Take this ring and throw it into a volcano to destroy it.
This cursed ring holds centuries of anger. To purify it, it must be thrown into a volcano... but we fear fire and can't go near it.
Hmm.
Oh, okay. Yeah!
I- I can do that quest for you.
Don't worry, I am the Chosen One!
Ah!
A ring!
Wow!
I don't know what a volcano is.
How is this supposed to help me save Justice?
They're gonna die!
They're gonna die if the volcano erupts!
Oh, wait. I don't know what a volcano is.
Let's just try to find the One Ping myself.
This box is a little suspicious.
Hmm...
Deliver to Weapon Shop.
Oh, cool! Is this for a quest?
Okay!
Bye! Bye!
Hey! I got a package!
I got you guys a package!
It's a gift from me!
I bought this!
I'll just leave it right here.
Yiah!
It looks just like the box of the BL novel set I lost! Thank you!
Your BL novels?!
No, no...
Don't- Don't lose sight of the quest, Gigi.
Woah!
Those are really cool swords!
If I bet- I bet I can save Justice with...
Ugh...
Why is it so heavy for cardboard?
Oh, oh my god.
I- I'm gonna put it back.
Ooh... This is why- This is why Justice has so much arm strength.
Oh my god.
Hahaha! That sword is pretty useless. It can undo cardboardification or something...
This sword is really cool. How much is it?
Huh?
What's that? Five dollars?!
Uh... I can't afford that.
But, uh, how about- How about I save them with the power of friendship?
Oh, another- another text box.
Is the One Ping even real?
I present a quest to you! Conquer it, and The One Ping shall be yours!
Would you craft 10 iron bars?
Okay, sounds easy. I can do that!
To craft 10 iron bars, you need to perform a freestyle dance and rap.
Gather 10 Grems with your performance to craft 10 iron bars.
What? I- I don't think that's how you craft an iron bar.
Ayo, you set, bro? Show us what you've got!
What did I get over here?
What are these sunglasses?
Grems...
This- this beat is kind of nasty.
Who let you have this in a shoe box?
Oh, okay!
I'm- I'm getting it. Oh, okay! I guess- I guess we're really doing this.
Okay.
Sent on a quest to save my friends
I don't really know what rhymes with friends
Old man wizard, take it from me
Evil flying birds looking for a treat
Don't even know if he's alive or not
But who really cares with the problems that I got?
Horse girls racing, my heart pacing
Gabi-abu-abi, ultimate skill activation
Then a bunch of Grems surrounded me
Asked me to forge some iron bars, you see?
Wait...
Wait a second.
Starting to realize what you meant by bars!
But my rap game is fire
And my dance is not desired
But if there's one thing that I'm not, it's definitely not a liar so I hope you don't mind
if I twerk up on it, you see!
There's a promise that I made to Fauna!
Yeah!
Oh, I'm twerking!
Ah, I don't know how to twerk.
I don't want to put in the work, you see
Twerking is a skill you have to, uh, you have to train up for, everyone.
And I ran out of rhymes 30 seconds ago.
All right, um...
I got dance moves and then...
Okay, I can't do that.
Mic drop!
Yo! Yo! Yo! That was amazing!
Really? You liked it?
You successfully crafted 10 iron bars!
Yippee! I got the iron bars!
Yippee!
Take this as a reward.
Huh?
Is that...
Is that what I think it is?
The One Ping is real!
Oh, where's my gauntlets?
Oyn oyn, olinlana doya.
Oh, is this yours? I found it down in the sewer.
Can I have it?
Wanowo, we wat, isia wonkayo.
If you want it back, throw the ring into the volcano.
Oh, cool. Thanks. I'm gonna go now.
Tati truly cursed. Halito with care, or semetiterible mi happen.
That ring is truly cursed. Handle it with care, or something terrible might happen.
Inu dare rowia, a feroia monis wi awaka...
If you dare throw it away, a ferocious monster will awaken...
Oh... Meat... Come to me.
I'm so hungry, I can't save Justice like this.
Meat? For me? For free?
Hey! Who toya ya cu ee tati?!
Hey! Who told you you could eat that?!
Whoa. Nice hat.
You... You doli mi ha?
You... You don't like my hat?
No, no, no. I think your hat is lovely. I... I love it.
Lovely? Really? You can eat as much meat as you want!
By the way, I'm looking for a straw hat. Do you know where we can find one?
I'll trade it if you complete my quest.
Oh, here we go again.
I want 26 pictures of giant rats.
Giant rats? Where do I find one of those?
Oh! Here they are!
Take your camera and capture family photos of all 26 of them!
Whoa. So it's a family of 26 rats?
I guess I can see why you want pictures of them. Oh, okay.
It's picture time. I'll get pictures of all 26 of them. Oh yeah!
Get, get in the frame. Let me get a picture of you.
One of them doesn't even look like a rat. That's a... That's a really big person.
What about down here? Oh. All right, one more. One more.
That's Grem!
What are you doing? You're not even a rat!
Okay. What about down here?
And look at those! They look like, just like Justice.
If Justice were rats, but they're cardboard.
Whoa. Okay, don't worry, I got you. I got every angle imaginable.
That's a computer mouse!
All right. And then look at this photo I took. And this one.
And this one! And this one! They're so cute.
All these rats are so cute. And this is awesome.
And this is a yummy looking rat. Yay!
How cute! I love them!!
Please accept this straw hat!
Ooh! A hat for me?
Yay! Now I have two items!
Oh! The stables are over there.
Maybe I can get the honkshoe from the stable.
Ah!
Ah! You scared me.
How are you doing?
Is everything going well?
Bad! I'm doing bad!
A few more quests might cheer you up! You should take the ring to...
It's like no one cares about me.
This is a cruel, evil world. Oh, the stables!
Ah. Oh, horses! Aw, hello.
Hi. Hi there. Hey!
Oh. Oh, would you... I can share.
Here you go. Eat up. Ah.
Is this horse okay?
Oh, no, I think... I think he's sleeping.
Okay, I think I can just... don't mind if I... I'll just take this. You don't need this, do you?
I've done it! I've gathered all three items by myself!
Yay! I am the hero of this kingdom!
Sewer Grem, you probably didn't think I'd get them all, but I did.
I got everything because I am the hero.
Dozo. For you.
Oh wow, you really managed to get everything I asked for!
Hold on, wait here. There's something special just for you!
Okay.
Ah, oh man. Can't believe I got everything.
Does that mean I saved Justice?
Oh, they're gonna be so proud of me.
Eh? Is there something?
No, no! Please, no! No! That way! No! Ah!
Ah... Oh... Ow... Owee...
Ugh...
Ow! Why does this keep happening to me?
Where am I? What is this?
This isn't my fantasy life.
A house?
Where am I going? What is...
Hey everyone, how's it going?
What's up, everyone? My name is Bae!
And my name is Bijou!
And together, we are BaeBijou!
Welcome to our Let's Play!
Today we are playing a new game called...
What is it called?
Gigi 3D!
Yeah, Gigi 3D. / I'm over here!
Yeah, it's a fresh new game, we are on the...
...alpha. We are the first ones to touch it!
So we've got exclusive footage here for you today. Let's get started!
So, the premise of this game is we control our character, Gigi.
Gigi 3D, probably, I don't know. And it's kind of like a real-life simulator game.
If I push this button right here, she should be able to sit down.
Let's see.
Oh, there we go! Wow! How did you do that?
Let's test out the controls. Let's try more complicated controls.
Can we make her sit on the sofa?
Let's see if she can act like a dog. You've got that dog in you!
Of course, of course! You would make me act like a dog.
Go, go! Louder! / *Barking*
Wow, look at those tricks! Oh my god!
Okay, that's enough, that's enough. Okay, stand back up.
So this is just the base game, right? / Guys, guys, look at the door.
So we've got the main living room, we've got the bedroom and the bathroom.
I think there's a kitchen attached. Kitchenette. Should we go check out the kitchen? Let's go see the kitchen.
Move character. / Move to the kitchen.
Come on, Gigi. / I don't want to.
Is there anything we can interact with in the kitchen?
Oh! Look, a knife! / Pick up the knife, pick it up right now!
What does she have? A knife! Pick up a knife!
Why is there so much input lag? Why is there input lag?
Maybe the connection is just a little bit slow, that's fine.
Now what? Put it into the stove! Yes, into the burning hot stove! / Please don't stab my soul.
Do you think they accounted for this kind of gameplay? / Oh!
Maybe that's something they'll add in the next update. That was kind of anticlimactic, oh well.
Pick up knife again. Pick up knife, always carry a knife. All right.
Shall we move on to another room? / Let's go enter door number one! Let's see what's in there.
Walk! Walk! Walk forward! / Go!
What is in that door? / Oh, she clipped. She clipped through the wall. We've got to report that bug.
Oh, there's a bathtub and there's a toilet!
Oh, oh, I know, I know! / Have you heard of Skibidi Toilet?
I'm going to make the character phase into the toilet with her head sticking out to become...
...Skibidi Toilet. Become one with the toilet, now!
Skibidi Toilet? I learn something new here every day.
Skibidi Toilet! / Skibidi dop dop dop yes yes, skibidi double u reeh reeh!
Look, is she happy? This is Skibidi Toilet.
Spin around! Spin your head around! / Spin my head right round...
Oh my god, this is great!
If you guys like what you see, make sure you like and subscribe!
Wow, okay!
And click the notification bell! - Yeah!
So you don't miss the next episode!
Yeah! And...
Pebbles, thank you for watching!
Bye!
Are they gone? I don't hear their voices anymore. Oh, thank God!
Oh, get me out of this toilet! Out of this Skibidi Toilet!
First you take over my body, then you make me a Skibidi toilet!
How do I get out of here?!
Look... look...
How could they... how could they torture me like this?
Why did they make me do all those things?
They didn't even feed me! And they didn't even say that I was a good girl after they made me do all those things!
And now I'm cold...
I have to take it out on this canvas.
If I just paint what I want, then maybe I'll be rewarded for it. Because...
...karma comes to good people. So...
...beautiful woman... boobs... yes...
Yes! I've done it!
My greatest work yet! My baby...
Hello? Gigi?
Hello? Knock knock!
Are you in there? Okay, I'm going to come in.
Oh my goodness...
This absolute masterpiece...
One of the lost works of Picasso? Or no, it has to be Leonardo da Vinci!
It's so incredible, I've never seen anything like it.
I can't believe that something like this is before my own eyes.
Gigi! Gigi, wake up!
Gigi, wake up!
Gigi, are you alright?
Something attacked me...
I don't know what kind of... - Why are you screaming?!
A beautiful woman...
Oh, yes! It's me! I came over just like you invited me.
Nerissa Ravencroft? - Yes, it is I.
Is that you? And not a painting?
No, but did you make this, Gigi? - I made this.
It's incredible.
You like it? I thought of you while making it.
Can you tell?
I can tell.
In fact, if... if it's so that I am your muse... maybe we could be together?
Really? Yes! No one's ever said that to me.
I've never wanted anything quite as much. After seeing this painting, the fire of my heart has been inflamed, and I feel like I cannot live without you, Gigi Murin.
Oh, tickle tickle tickle tickle tickle!
Don't scream now. - You're tickling me.
You know what? I've thought of thinking...
...thought thought about thinking, I've thought of it, and I've come up with a thing.
We should get married.
Oh, I thought you'd never ask! - Really? Really? Why would you think that?
Do you want me? - I want you so bad!
You have no idea how bad I want you.
Let's go! We have to go consummate our marriage! - Wait, what?!
I don't know if I'm ready for that!
I don't know!
そう簡単な祈りにちょっと
To such a simple prayer, just a bit...
ランラララ
Lan la la la...
淡々と消える簡単
Fading away indifferently, so easy...
今から緞帳が上がるから
Because the stage curtain is about to rise.
静かな退場をあとにさよなら
Farewell after a quiet exit.
えい、えってってっていや
Hey, eh-teh-teh-teh-yah!
言いかけていた言葉 ひとつ消えて
One of the words I was about to say faded away...
ただ二つ、ぽつりと落とされた
Merely two drops were let fall
狂기에また坂を下る
Descending the slope once more in madness
下らない言葉に身を任せるように
As if giving myself over to worthless words
零れて胸の裏返りのように濁る
They spill over and muddy, like turning my heart inside out
受け止めたい言葉が自分さえ抱えられず
Unable to hold onto even the words I want to accept myself
持て余したそれを今日も持っている
I still carry them today, not knowing what to do with them
歪んだ声はからからに
This warped voice runs dry
呪いは焼いておくの クスリ何を言うべきか分からなくて
I'll burn the curse away, a quick giggle, not knowing what to say
感じてたものが固く結ばれていた
What we felt was tightly bound together
同じように違う 何かが違う
Alike yet different, something is off
いつまで行こうか
How long shall we go on?
どこまで行けるのか
How far can we go?
定かじゃないなら何を思うの
If it's uncertain, what are you thinking?
僕らが離れるなら
If we are to drift apart...
僕らが迷うなら
If we are to lose our way...
その度何回も繋がれるように
So that we can reconnect time and time again
ここにいてくれるなら
If you'll stay here with me...
離さずにいられたなら
If I could have held on to you...
まだ誰も知らない感覚に触れていく
We'll touch upon feelings that no one yet knows
L-A-S-T-T-Y
不安とは相も変わって変わり果てていく
Anxiety, true to form, continues to morph completely
実際は誰も変わりはなく
While in reality, no one has changed
今日 楽とは嘘でならす
Declaring today's comfort with a lie
誇りの前にここで立っているのが証拠
Standing here before pride is the evidence
都合の良い願いを同じように同じように囁く
Whispering convenient wishes in the exact same way
どこから行こうか 何を失うか
Where shall we start? What will we lose?
定かじゃないから言葉が解けない
Since it's not certain, the words won't unravel
僕らが救われるなら
If we are to be saved...
これ以上ないなら
If there is nothing more than this...
その度何回も逃げ出せるように
So that we can escape time and time again
心が守れるように
So that our hearts can be protected...
奪われないように
So that they won't be stolen away...
互いに隠して身体を預けてよ
Let's hide each other and entrust our bodies
Lalala...
君と泣く
Crying with you...
君と笑う
Laughing with you...
君と怒る
Being angry with you...
君と歌う
Singing with you...
君と踊る
Dancing with you...
君と生きる
Living with you...
いつまで続くのだろうと
Wondering how long this will continue
同じように同じように呟く
I mutter in the exact same way
今は忘れないよう刻まれた空気を
For now, so I don't forget the engraved atmosphere...
これから何度思い出すのだろう
...how many times will I recall it from now on?
僕らが
If we...
僕らが離れるなら
If we are to drift apart...
僕らが迷うなら
If we are to lose our way...
その度何回も繋がれるように
So that we can reconnect time and time again
ここにいてくれるなら
If you'll stay here with me...
離さずにいられたなら
If I could have held on to you...
まだ誰も知らない
Through the things...
感覚で
...no one...
僕の生きてるすべてを
...knows yet, I'll confirm...
確かめて正しくして
...my entire existence and make it right.
L-A-S-T-T-Y
Oh, husband. I'm so happy to be living a domestic life with you, Gigi Murin.
Well... in your awesome house,
with your awesome kitchen, and your awesome floor, and this awesome couch.
Wife...
...husband.
I've never been married before.
Me neither.
What am I supposed to do? How am I supposed to take care of you?
Take care of me? You're so sweet. No one's ever wanted to do that.
I want to take care of you. I've dreamed of this forever...
...and ever.
Oh, my goodness!
And ever. And ever. Gigi Murin!
Please, not in front of... Not in front of the studio audience!
Oh, my beautiful, beautiful wife. How far does your leg go up?
As far as you want it to!
I see. That's enough.
Not in front of the studio audience.
Not in front of the studio audience. I can't believe you did that.
Me?
If you say so, husband. I can't believe I'm such a dirty, dirty girl in front of this audience and everyone.
That's... That's only for me, my dirty, dirty girl.
Yes! I wouldn't want anyone else to see me like that but you.
I should do something for you. That is what a Gigi Murin should do.
Yes, I would love that.
I should make you some toast.
Some toast for me?!
Yes, for you.
You're so sweet.
Have you ever cooked before?
No, never.
Never?
Never. I don't even know how to use a microwave.
Really?
Yes, really.
Well, I only have one thing here and it's toast.
Wow, you're so amazing.
Did you make the bread yourself too?
I made it.
Whoa!
Oh, it's been on the floor, that's even better!
You stepped there!
Watch me, watch me flip it, okay?
Yes, yes, I'm watching. Oh! Oh!
Watch... watch this.
Wait, wait!
Wait, wait, I have a solution.
Okay, flip it.
Yes!
You're amazing!
Ah, that made me really hungry.
Do you mind if I eat this toast first?
Of course you can.
Anything for you...
Really? You're such a sweet wife!
That looks tasty.
I have to use the bathroom, my sweet.
Oh, of course.
By all means, anything you need.
If I look through the doorknob hole...
I can see Gigi on the toilet.
Oh, Gigi, I just have to tell you...
These last few hours together have been absolute domestic bliss.
I don't think there's any moment in my life that's been...
...as amazing as this.
Are you still in there?
Oh, sorry.
How's the toast?
It's really good! I wish you could try some.
Oh, yeah, me too. Maybe next time.
I made this for you, so... what if it was poisoned, you know? So I had to check.
You're so thoughtful!
Well, Nerissa Ravencroft, I've been doing a lot of thinking while I was on the toilet.
Yes?
And I don't...
I don't... I don't know...
Don't say another word.
I don't know what a family entails.
I completely understand.
Would you be able to teach me?
Of course. I can teach you anything.
Really?
Of course. I'm a 10,000-year-old demon. We can do anything you want together.
You can teach me anything?
Anything.
Anything?
Any... anything?
Anything your heart desires.
Well, I shouldn't keep my beautiful wife waiting.
But I have a tummy ache.
You have a tummy ache?
Will you wait for me?
Of course. I'll wait forever for you.
Okay, hold on. I don't think I should be eating this toast all by myself.
Don't worry.
Let me slide it under the door for you.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Oh, wow!
Is it good?
So delicious!
Is it tasty?
It's so tasty!
Skibidi toilet!
Never has there been bread made...
...this amazing!
I'm glad that I made such beautiful toast for you.
Me too! It was my first time...
Hey!
I finished it all.
All of it?
All of it. It's all in my stomach.
Is it really yummy?
So delicious.
I'm glad.
I was really, really nerv- I still am nervous, because you're so...
...you're so beautiful...
...and I'm just a little guy on a toilet.
A little guy?
...and I have a tummy ache...
Don't worry.
...and there's just so much wrong with me. But you're... there's everything right with you.
But that's how I feel about you!
Really?
With me, everything is wrong, but when we're together...
...everything is perfect.
No one has ever said that to me before!
My love, why are you crying?
I'm sick and tired of these walls separating us. Nerissa, come in here!
Let's break them down!
Sit... sit on my lap, Nerissa.
Sit on your lap?
I will. Anything you ask for, I will do.
How about though we move from this porcelain...
...my porcelain throne?
Yeah, and we move somewhere a little more...
Okay.
Well, I'm... I'm done.
Yeah?
Did you wash your hands?
No.
Okay. It's better this way.
Let's hold hands.
Yes, let's hold hands.
Hold my hand.
I'm holding your hand.
Let's go to the bedroom together.
Yeah, to the bedroom!
Well, Gigi...
What's the matter?
I'm... I'm shy.
Don't be shy. It's...
I've never done this before!
You know, Gigi, the truth is, I know I said I'd teach you anything, but...
...I've never done this before either.
Really?
Then how are we supposed to do it if you've never...
...done such a thing before! Who's going to teach me?
We're going to learn together.
You can just learn from nothing?
Of course.
That's not something you can just do!
We'll find it out. How do you think the first humans learned things, Gigi?
I don't know!
Why are you asking me that?
Philosophical... It's pillow talk. Anyway...
Oh, oh, oh, okay.
Well... Shall we?
Well, now that you've brought it up...
...the first humans probably learned things by doing things.
Yes! So let's just do it then.
Okay!
I can't wait another moment.
That was enough!
That was too much! That was way too much!
Gigi Murin, you monster!
Oh, I'm sorry! I was trying to be really gentle.
You did great.
Really?
Yes, it was amazing!
Well, I'm glad that we could spend our first day in the bedroom together as a married couple.
Yes, but Gigi, there's something strange going on. Did you transfer your stomach ache to me?
I don't think so. You can't just give a tummy ache to someone.
But it really, it really hurts. Maybe I should...
...use the bathroom?
I don't think so, but oh...
Gigi...
Wait a moment. Gigi, your fingers!
No! No!
No, I'm not ready! I'm not ready!
You forgot to wear full gloves!
No! How is this...
I can't, we can't!
We don't have the money!
Gigi, I'm sorry!
I didn't tell you to get... This house is barely holding together!
Gigi, it hurts! Doctor! Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor! Doctor, please!
My wife, she's in pain! Can you please help her? Please, Doctor! Please!
Please help me!
What? Hello? Are you going to help her?
Hello? Why are you laughing? I'm giving birth here!
She is literally, she is literally giving birth and you're just laughing at her?
What kind of doctor... Ah, wait till I go on the internet and leave bad reviews about you!
Your days are numbered! You're going out of business, and you're going to go bankrupt!
Gigi! Gigi, the baby!
It won't wait another minute!
Gigi!
I got it! It's safe!
Our child.
It's our baby.
It's a... it's a beautiful egg!
It is such a beautiful egg.
Wow! We didn't need a doctor after all.
You're so... You're a natural.
You're so good at that.
It seems like we're both a natural at a lot of things.
Yes! Wow!
You know, I'm a little impatient. I kind of wonder, what are you? What are you in there? Hello?
Hey. Are you... Hello?
I don't... Are you going to just shake the baby?
Yeah. Wake up!
Oh! Goodness!
It's our son!
Our son!
He's so cute!
Let's, let's let them hold the baby.
Yes. Should we name him? Should we name him?
You're not going to hold it like a mommy?
Should, should we name him?
Yeah, we should name him.
Maybe we should let them name him.
Them?
Them.
Them out there?
Them out there.
Them out?
Yeah. They've been watching us this whole time, you know.
What?
Do you guys have an idea to name our baby?
They've been watching... give birth?
They're throwing name suggestions.
They're what?
Yeah.
Those are some great suggestions. What do you think?
All terrible.
I'm going to name him Nerigi.
Nerigi. Yeah, because it's like your name and then my name, and together...
It's perfect.
It's just a happy family. Just you, me, Nerigi. And then now you're a beautiful mother, and now I'm also a beautiful father.
What else can we do?
I don't know. Maybe you should go somewhere else while I take care of the baby.
よし、よし...
There, there...
Why are you still watching me? Go away!
Go away.
Better get the mail for my wife.
I think giving birth is really expensive.
We'll have to pay the bills. I don't have any money though.
God, I hope these aren't bills.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
I'm... I'm...
Help!
Help! I'm drowning!
Wait, did you... did you leave your controller on?
Oh, maybe I like dropped it on the floor and the controller like... We're not even touching the controller, wait.
Wait, she's going for the ladder! We're taking it out! Take it out!
Take it out! Yeah, take the ladder out! Take it out!
The liquid of water is filling your lungs.
The air is slowly moving out of your body, you're drowning, Helen.
Wait, she's kind of cute though. Oh my god, wait. What's happening?
Oh my god, did you see that?
Oh, is her house on fire? My house might be on fire. Ah, whatever.
Filling your lungs, the water, you are slowly suffocating from the inside.
I hear the inner monologue.
Bae, help me!
I think there is a... a quiz function. Oh, really? I think if, like, maybe...
...the character can answer the quiz correctly, the ladder will come back as a prize. No quiz! I don't want a quiz! No quiz!
Too much water! Oh, are you ready?
Are you ready for the quiz? Are you ready? No!
Let me out!
What is the name of the hypothetical particle that mediates the force of gravity
in quantum field theory, and has not yet been observed experimentally?
A. Photon, B. Gluon... C. Graviton, or D. Neutrino.
Please answer correctly, or else you will die.
What do you want me... A? I don't care! A!
Is it A?!
The answer was... C, Graviton. No!
Wah-wah-wah-wah. You failed.
Maybe the next character will know. Try harder next time.
Oh well. Boring.
Oh, she dead.
Took my ladder away! Help! Someone help me! I don't know how to swim!
Mori Calliope! Give me a hand! Mori Calliope, I'm drowning!
Get your... Mori Calliope!
She's flashing me... while I'm dying? Mori, there's a better time for that!
Stop! Stop, I can't look!
Mori Calliope... put that away. Put...
Hey... Hey...
Listen to me. I'm drowning! Listen to me. Okay.
You made me watch dancing fruits on TV. You liked it!
You made me dance next to horses. I liked that. Fuck you.
Wait, wait, we can talk about it! Mori Calliope, wait, wait! Die, idiot!
Mori Calliope!
So... someone help me, I'm drowning. Bae, Bae, you're killing me!
They're literally... they are killing me. Oh, Mori Calliope, she's killing me.
I'm alive! I'm not... I'm not drowning!
But my wife, my child... my beautiful wife and child, where are they?
Why am I in the Gram Kingdom? What about Nerissa?
My beautiful wife!
Nerissa, where did you go? I love you!
Why... why is everything on fire?
What?
There's a dragon here?
My friends are made of cardboard!
They are not fire resistant. Oh no. Okay, I see that the Grams are doing their best to save them.
Okay, Grams... What... What's this one doing? What are you up to?
Oh, you are not helping at all.
It's... It's okay, little Gram. Your arms will reach one day.
These Grems on the other hand,
you have magic!
Wow!
Where'd you learn this?
You guys are so talented.
Not you, though.
It's okay.
One day.
Grems, Grems are working really hard, so...
I, me, Gigi Murin the hero...
is here to save the day!
Oh.
This must be my hero weapon, as all heroes have a hero weapon.
Okay.
Let's see. Oh.
One million dollars?!
What?
Oh, kingdom can save itself, I am out!
Oh, wait, a catapult!
Of course!
Of course, obviously! Okay.
I'll help with this.
Don't worry, Grems. Let me...
What, what ammo is here?
Oh.
Okay, let's...
let's just pick this up.
Hup...
Yay!
Let's go, Grem! Let's save the kingdom.
Let's save the kingdom together!
Yeah!
Huh.
We barely scratched it.
I don't know what to do.
There's, there's just no other choice.
I'm gonna have to pull out...
that move.
Yeah! Yeah, that move.
My ultimate move!
All right, everyone, are you ready to see my...
ultimate move?
Okay.
Here goes!
Ah! Stop!
Oji-chan! You scared me!
Wait...
No!
You took...
you took the fire breath, Oji-chan!
Stop it! Stop!
You're gonna die!
Die! No!
No, you're getting hurt!
Please, I need you!
If you die here, who's gonna tell me how to defeat the dragon?!
No, no, please, please!
No...
You're getting hurt.
No! No!
Are you okay?
Oji-chan?
(groaning)
You saved me!
You must...
save
What, what is it?
this...
kingdom.
The kingdom?
How am I supposed to save it without you?!
No!
Oji-chan, no!
I don't know how I'm supposed to save the kingdom and destroy the dragon!
It's not taking any damage!
Get up...
Help! Call the guard
wizard graveyard
Grems come and pray, Gremdal the Grey
Danger is here, a dragons appear
Come seize the day, fight and we slay
Gigi Murin, here at the scene
Look and behold, legends foretold
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
Where did you come from?
From near and far, hit by a car
There's so many of you!
Gremurin, come outside to pray, oh
Like, like 15 of you!
gremurin, gremurin
Wait, what are you singing about?
About me?
Help! Call the guard, Grems come and pray
Danger is here, a dragons appear
That's right. I am a hero.
Come seize the day, fight and we slay
I can save the day!
Gigi Murin, here at the scene
Through the power of these children singing for me...
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
I can do anything! Yeah!
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
Yeah, I can do it all!
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
Okay, okay, what should I do?
From near and far, hit by a car
What should I do, Grems? What should I do? I don't know.
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Through the power of interpretive dance!
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
That's the only way we can destroy a dragon...
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
...because it has not been taking any physical damage.
Gremurin, come outside to pray, oh
The best way to defeat this dragon is through mental damage!
I've never done a worm before. I'm gonna do a worm!
Help! Call the guard, Grems come and pray
I did it, Grems! I did it!
Danger is here, a dragons appear
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
I... I'm not an interpretive dancer!
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gigi, Gigi is here. Don't worry.
Another cartwheel! A second one, even!
Yeah, and then, and then a worm?
Is it working?
Is the dragon being...
...cringed out by me?
Oh no, I cannot do this.
Ah! Ah!
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi, Gigi Murin
My name... They're saying my name.
Is it working? Tell me, children!
Is the dragon being affected by me?
[emotional vocal solo]
What is this?
This power I'm feeling...
Oh no...
It's surging in... in my veins!
Oh...
Oh man...
I feel it!
Ah!
They don't call me...
...the Fister for nothing!
Yeah!
gremurin, gremurin
That's me...
...the Fister...
...Gigi Murin...
...Holo-Live English Justice!
I've done it!
Gigi Murin has done it!
I defeated the dragon!
I did it!
Oji-chan, it was all thanks to you and the fifteen children! But it was all thanks to you and the fifteen children that I did it!
Yeah!
Oji-chan... Wait, you're still dead?!
No!
No, I thought... I thought my power of dance could have saved you!
Oji-chan, no!
Oji-chan!
You're okay!
The power of dance does save everyone!
You're okay, right? You're not possessed, are you?
Oh, what is this?
Oh, what are you doing?
Oh, what is happening?
Oh, oh god! What's... what's happening?
What the...?
What the heck is happening?
Oji-chan?
Oji-chan! You're okay!
I've done it!
Yeah!
Behold, the darkness has lifted...
...from the dragon's soul.
My final desperate strike...
...has shattered its cruel memories.
No longer a beast of fury, it has been reborn...
...as an innocent baby dragon!
にっこり調査隊 おはこんばんちは how are you?
Smiling Survey Team! Good day, afternoon, and evening! How are you?
今日も今日とて最高です おぉ~わんだほい!
Today is as great as any other day! Oh, wonderhoy!
にっこり^^調査隊のテーマ
[Title: Smiling^^
Survey Team's Theme]
はい！我々は世界の笑顔を調査する！
Yes! We will investigate the world's smiles!
はい隊長、俺に名案が...
Yes, Captain! I have a great idea...
却下！
Rejected!
って、まだ何も言ってないんだが？
But I haven't even said anything yet!
もー、とにかくあれだほら、カナブンは一見にしかず？
Jeez! Anyway, you know, is a drone beetle worth a thousand words?
あぁ、百聞は一見に如かずだねぇ
Ah, seeing is believing, you mean.
それそれ！つまり虫取り？
That's it! So, bug catching?
違うって、隊長！
No, Captain!
提案があります！
I have a proposal!
ぜひ聞かせてほしいものだな！
I'd certainly love to hear it!
とりあえず...
For now...
とりあえず？
For now?
とりあえず出発しよう、ノープランで！
For now, let's set off with no plan!
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
え？出発進行！
Eh? Full speed ahead!
ちょっと待ってって！旅支度くらいさせろー！
I said wait! At least let me pack my bags!
では、持ち物チェック始めます！
Okay, starting the baggage check!
まずは基本のパスポート（持った！）
First is the basic passport! (Got it!)
おやつは500円まで（あ、杖忘れた！）
Snacks up to 500 yen! (Ah, I forgot my staff!)
えええ〜！
What?!
モバイルバッテリー（持った！）
Mobile battery! (Got it!)
志は（持った！もちろん！）
Your determination? (Got it! Of course!)
旅の途中で（私がいる）
In the middle of our journey... (I'm right here!)
しかも普通じゃない（誰のことかな）
And we're not ordinary! (I wonder who that is?)
にっこりこりこりこりこりあんな
Smile, smile, smile, smile, smile!
あっちもこっちもそっちも100万回サンキュー
Thank you a million times here, there, and everywhere!
君の笑顔も（もっと）もっと見せて（見せて！）
Show us your smile (more) even more! (Show us!)
大人も子供も関係ねえぜ これぞ一流のエンターテイナー！
Adults and kids, it doesn't matter! This is a top-notch entertainer!
私、待っているわ いつか夢を叶えてやるって
I'm waiting! Ready to make my dreams come true someday!
（We can do it!）
(We can do it!)
このにっこりに触れて もっと胸膨らむ明日へ
Touching this smile, toward a tomorrow filled with even more hope!
グッ！
Yeah!
はい、注目！
Attention, please!
にっこり調査隊の、大隊長のご紹介！
Allow me to introduce the Captain of the Smile Survey Team!
さあ、いっさいがっさい調査の態勢！
Now, let's prepare to survey absolutely everything!
今だ、悪をてんてんどんどん成敗！
Right now, let's punish evil over and over!
密着調査報告書その１！
First report from our close-up survey!
おひげは、全然ちがいます！
The beard is completely different!
おばけも、全然ちがいます！
The ghosts are completely different!
やだ！めっちゃ怖！
Oh no! That's so scary!
大変です！全然全然にっこりが足りてません！
This is bad! There are not nearly enough smiles!
とりあえず、
For now,
for now,
とりあえず待って、ティンと来たな！
wait, just hold on! I've got an idea!
だな！
Indeed!
お前が言うな！
Don't say that!
落ち着こう？
Let's calm down?
じゃあ、お持ち物チェック始めまーす！
Okay, let's begin checking our gear!
おう、じゃあいつものな！
Yeah, let's do the usual!
パ、パ、パスポート持った？
P-P-Passport, do you have it?
はい！
Yes!
パ、パ、パンツは忘れた！
P-P-Pants, I forgot them!
Oh, my!
モバイルバッテリー持った？
Do you have your portable charger?
もった！
Got it!
志は持った？
Do you have your high ambitions?
もちろん！お国柄とか
Of course! Nationalities or
老若男女
young or old, male or female,
あんまし関係ない
it doesn't really matter!
ワールドワイドだぜ！
We are worldwide!
あっちもこっちも世界も
Even this, that, and the whole world
まだまだ、すっ捨てたもんじゃない、ねっ！
aren't so bad after all, right?
にっこり、にっこり、にっこり、お利口さん！
Smile, smile, smile, be a good kid!
イーアルサンスー ウェルカム！
One, two, three, four, welcome!
君の笑顔が
Your smile
調査対象さ！
is the target of our survey!
Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah!
メンタルドッカン、ドッカン、ロケットケーキ
Mental boom-boom rocket cake...
お砂糖も、スパイスだって、てんこ盛り！
Both sugar and spice are piled high!
私だっていつか、夢を叶えてやるって
Even I will make my dreams come true one day!
We can do it!
このにっこりに触れて、もっと胸膨らみました、とさ！
Felt those smiles, and my chest puffed up with pride!
しょんぼりはにっこりに変換！
Turn those frowns into smiles!
うちらに任せれば、メイクユアスマイル！
Leave it to us, make your smile!
晴れの時だって
Even when it's sunny,
雨の時だって
even when it's rainy,
かき混ぜちゃって、スパイスだって！
mix them all up, even the spices!
完璧だ！
Perfect!
にっこり、にっこり、にっこり、お利口さん！
Smile, smile, smile, be a good kid!
大人も子供も
Adults and children alike
めっちゃめちゃ関係、もちろんどちらも調査対象だ！
are absolutely included! Both are definitely our survey targets!
Way, Way, Way, Way, Way!
私だっていつか、夢を叶えてやるって
Even I will make my dreams come true one day!
We can do it!
このにっこりに触れて、もっと胸膨らみました、とさ！
Felt those smiles, and my chest puffed up with pride!
That's not all! That's right!
You didn't expect this, oh, you didn't expect this...
There's 3D Merch! Yay!
You too, you watching at home can own your very own...
Grem Hand In Cushion! What does that mean?
You can put your hands in the Grem!
You can remember all the good times that we had in the Grem Kingdom
with Oji-chan! Yay! Yay!
And you can do so many things with this Grem, like stick your hands in it,
which I said. You can stick your hands in the Grem!
And you can sleep on it, and you can squish it,
and you can cherish it, and you can love it! And it's very soft,
and very squishy! Just watch Oji-chan play with it. Doesn't it look cool?
3Dお披露目グッズの登場だ！
The 3D showcase merch is here!
Yay!
見よ、このグレムのもちもちのハンドインクッションじゃよ！
Look at this squishy Grem Hand In Cushion!
So cool!
いっぱい可愛がっておくれよ、頼んだぞ。いやー！
Take good care of it, please. Yes!
Yay!
Thank you everyone for coming to my 3D Live today!
I worked really, really hard on it!
And thank you to the staff who is, who is overseeing me!
And thank you to Oji-chan for being here, and thank you for the Grems!
And thank you for Mococo, Fuwawa, and Nerissa, and Bae, and Biboo,
and Justice for being here, a part of my 3D Live!
This was so much fun! Oh, it was so awesome!
Oh, thank you! And I'm looking forward to doing more 3D things for you guys!
Yay! Yep, that's all!
And don't forget there is more 3D debuts next week!
So make sure you tune in
because all of Justice has been working so hard! Okay? Okay!
Bye everyone! Oh, see you later!
Bye-bye!
Grems, thank you for being a part of my journey! It's because of you that I'm here.
[Gigi's Letter] Grems, thank you for being a part of my journey! It's because of you that I'm here.
Sometimes it still doesn't feel real that I get to be here with you all.
You are my passion! You are my strength! I will keep working hard.
I could say thank you a million times and it still wouldn't feel like enough.
But for all the times you've made me laugh, thank you for always supporting me.
Stay silly! - Gigi